- Miss Kano!
- Hm?
Did she leave already?
Something the matter, ma'am?
She left her phone behind.
I can get it to her.
She lent me her umbrella after all.
It's the least I can do.
Oh!
Found her!
[gasps]
INOMATA
[inaudible]
Why is Chinatsu at Taiki's house?
It doesn't matter, I should get home.
I'll ask him tomorrow. Oh.
Hey! Taiki Inomata!
What in the heck is going on here?
[gasps] Hina?
Why is Chinatsu Kano,
Eimei's treasure, at your house,
and why did you, Taiki Inomata,
Eimei's potato face,
just say, "Welcome back" to her?
I demand an explanation!
[Taiki exclaims]
[grunts]
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
EPISODE 6
WISH ME LUCK
[Taiki] The truth is...
TAIKI
CHINATSU
[Hina] I see...
So while Chinatsu's parents
are working overseas, she is...
living together with you and your family.
Got it.
Sorry. You've been so supportive
with me having a crush on her,
and I kept this from you.
I'm pretty shocked if I'm being honest.
To find out how little you trust me.
I'm sorry.
And here I was thinking we were besties.
I thought you were totally nuts
going after Chinatsu.
JUMP
Turns out, you've been
coming home every day
and spending time alone with her.
[Taiki grunts]
Whe... where is this going?
Stay still for five hours,
and then I'll forgive you.
What?
I know that it's not just about you,
Chinatsu is wrapped up in this, too,
so I get why you
wouldn't go around telling people.
And I did say that I would help you,
but I admit I've been slacking a bit.
With that said, I'm still pissed at you,
so don't move.
Hina. Thanks a lot.
Also, this is the best you can do
in two months? It's pathetic.
Hey!
There you have it.
They're living together.
I thought they seemed close lately.
Makes sense.
Taiki had a crush on her
before she moved in.
And you don't usually live
with someone of the opposite sex
if you can't stand them.
Which means...
I'm so sorry.
Oh.
What on earth am I doing?
EIMEI PRIVATE HIGH SCHOOL
[piano music playing]
[all exclaiming]
[coach] That's our Chono! Sensational!
[Niina] You're so cool.
All in a day's work.
Keep this up, and once you hit nationals,
you could podium, or who knows,
maybe you'll take it all!
Please leave it to me.
I am Hina Chono.
Named for the butterfly,
I'll honor my namesake
and dance beautifully.
You're speaking in riddles.
You never disappoint.
- [girl] Keep it up, Hina.
- [Niina] That was perfect, wasn't it?
- [girl] Totally.
- Hina?
I'm gonna take a little break.
[moody music playing]
I almost missed a step
in that run-through.
And that made my next move a beat behind.
I wasn't focusing enough
on my lines, either.
I gotta practice till its automatic.
Everyone's counting on me.
I can't disappoint them.
If I make even a single mistake...
Psh, it's fine.
This is Hina Chono we're talking about!
[exclaims excitedly, grunts]
- Whatcha doing?
- Hina!
Oh. Nothing in particular.
Nothing at all, huh?
Hiding more secrets, are we?
[Taiki] I am not.
One of my toenails dug into my skin.
Ew, I don't wanna know that, stop it!
That's why I didn't tell you before.
[sighs] Well, don't forget the antiseptic.
[exclaims softly]
A wish bracelet?
Do you wear stuff like that?
It's just... [sighs]
Chinatsu gave it to me.
Huh?
The two of you must be dating.
- So you're hiding that, too?
- Huh?
This wasn't anything romantic!
We're just two people trying to make it
to nationals. It's that kind of thing.
- That's just beautiful.
- Oh, can it, you jerk!
[Hina] "Two people trying
to make it to nationals," huh?
- Keep it up, keep it up!
- Run, run, go!
That must mean...
whenever practice gets tough,
they think of the other person,
[sad piano music playing]
and remember that someone else out there
is working as hard as they are.
[Haryu] Taiki!
Focus up!
- Yeah!
- [Hina] And that keeps them going.
I guess that's what they have together.
[music stops]
[gasps]
[sad piano music continues]
Why am I crying?
Prepping for qualifiers
has me all moody. No, thank you.
This is something I need to handle alone.
And being alone... is fine.
[exclaims softly]
[girl 1] She missed it again.
[girl 2] She's done that a lot lately.
Miss Chono. Are you feeling all right?
Oh, boy!
I was up late watching TV
and didn't sleep well.
Sleep is critical, you know.
Sorry about that.
- [Kyo] She seems kind of out of it.
- That's rare for her.
She never misses a beat,
even when she gets nervous.
Hey...
Hold on, that means
she's way off her game.
You better give me 3,000 to keep looking.
Maybe you're right about that,
or maybe she's mad at you about something.
Huh?
[Hina] Yep, yep, yep. That's for the best.
Chinatsu might pull away if she sees Taiki
getting friendly with other girls.
They're not just running into each other
in the hallway,
they live under the same roof.
He doesn't need my help anymore.
I don't wanna kill their vibe, either.
- Let's go visit the potty!
- You don't have to say it so loud.
[Hina] I'll take a step back
from being his friend for now.
I even apologized to her.
Covered in issues of Jump.
What does that mean?
Hina, maybe it's time for a little break?
I know the qualifiers are soon,
but you're killing yourself.
I am 100% okay.
Failing is part of success, you know?
But I'm gonna go take
a mental break, though.
[both exclaim]
COLD DRINKS
[Hina] Whatever I say,
I know they're still worried about me.
For someone who's known for her bravado,
this is pathetic.
I need to get it together.
BIOLOGY CLUB
Taiki's stubborn like that boar.
- [vice principal] Miss Chono.
- Hm?
Mr. Vice Principal.
I read your interview in the newspaper!
Goodness, you're not just talented
in rhythmic gymnastics,
you're wonderful in an interview, too!
Thank you very much.
So, tell me,
how is the routine coming along lately?
Qualifiers are coming up, huh?
It's a ten, sir!
Ah. Very good to hear.
You're quite the disciplined,
self-starting type, aren't you?
Just what we'd expect
from the daughter of Hirohiko Chono.
- He did represent Japan after all!
- [chuckles]
Might there be a chance
your father would stop by?
We'd love to give him a big Eimei hello.
I'll pass that along!
Please do!
What a fine student we have here!
EXPECTATIONS
4TH PLACE
I have enough weighing
on my shoulders, thank you.
DAD - ARTICLE - CONCERNS - TRAINING
It's not like
I'm that amazing of a person.
I'm just a regular high school first-year.
It's times like these...
I wish I could joke around
with that idiot goody-two-shoes.
The guy who only ever thinks
about the next step,
and keeps moving forward.
Keep it up!
[gasps softly]
[whimpers]
That's right.
I've gotta handle this alone.
[uplifting music playing]
Good for her.
Looks like our girl is back.
[Hina] All right.
Didn't make one mistake today.
But I'm still feeling a little shaky.
I need to win the prefecturals first,
then get in my best shape
before nationals.
[boy] Oh, hold on. I, uh...
I forgot something. I'll run and grab it.
[Hina gasps]
Oh, I'm sorry! Are you okay?
- What happened?
- Oh, I just...
- [heart beating]
- [Hina breathing shakily]
It hurts...
Did I sprain it?
I can just tape it.
But what if the pain pulls my focus?
No, seriously, are you okay?
[Hina] I'm not
in my best shape to begin with.
What do I do?
[Taiki] Can you stand?
[Hina gasps]
Huh?
It's your left ankle?
Come on. Let's have
the nurse check you out.
All good! I don't need help there.
I appreciate it, but I'm okay, you can go.
Oh, okay.
Go on. You don't want Chinatsu
to see us together.
See us?
I'm not thinking about that right now!
You're constantly acting like the world
revolves around the "Great Hina Chono,"
then, when you actually need help,
you overthink it.
- I'll tell the advisor.
- Yeah. Thanks, dude.
It's moments like these
when you should put yourself first.
[gasps softly]
[Taiki] All right, hold on. Up we go.
[Hina] Stop it.
No.
I don't wanna find out what this is.
NURSE'S OFFICE
Seems like there's nothing wrong with it.
Nothing... wrong... with it?
You probably knocked it when you fell.
You do have a bruise, but the pain
should subside in a few minutes.
You might be more sensitive to it
because the qualifiers are coming up.
Let's ice it to be on the safe side.
Looks like somebody cried wolf.
It felt real to me!
I've been under
a lot of pressure you know.
[groans] And truth be told,
I haven't been sleeping well, either.
INOMATA COUNSELING
Uh-huh. And when did these symptoms start?
The worst counselor imaginable.
Is that a prompt for your next skit?
I'm gonna stay with you, so lay it on me.
What do they mean
by "the star athlete's daughter"?
I mean, I respect my dad and all,
but I got me here, not him.
People thinking my achievements
are 'cause my dad happens to have been
on the national team sucks!
- [Taiki] It doesn't end, does it?
- Our coach just smiles with no advice.
The way things stand, there's one person
who I don't think I can beat.
That's not like you.
You never called any gymnast unbeatable.
[chuckles]
I can't say that I've ever seen someone
in this way before.
The judge is so devoted to her.
What?
You mean she gets scored
based on who she is,
rather than her actual performance?
What can I say, the judge loves her.
Well, that judge can eat my shorts!
I'm pissed off.
Right?
I'm pissed off, too.
But then, she's terribly attractive, so...
I can totally see why.
She catches everyone's attention,
but she's not stuck up about it.
And she works as hard as anyone.
Up against such an opponent,
even I, the Great Chono,
wants to back down and run away.
We both know you'd never run away.
Huh?
You have this kind of
indomitable warrior spirit, you know?
[yelling]
For one, you really hate to lose,
and your pride plays a role in that, too.
But more than anything, you're the kind
who won't back down without a fight.
That is just who you are.
[grunts]
You're pissing me off!
I can think of plenty of scenarios
where the best thing to do is run!
I see the error of my ways, I'm sorry!
Although... you're totally right about me.
[door opens]
That's enough.
It's time to get back to practice.
[Taiki] All right, back we go.
How's your ankle doing?
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Just remember, if you lose,
you have no excuse.
I'm not losing.
- Hey, Taiki.
- Hm?
Do you mind, um...
wishing me luck?
Good luck!
[chuckles]
[happy piano music playing]
Psh, you think I needed that?
[Taiki] You made me say it!
[laughter and applause]
Miss Chono, congratulations!
That performance certainly deserved
first place in the qualifiers.
- Great job.
- You killed it!
[Hina chuckles]
You know, I think
I might've been worried over nothing.
Well, good for her.
It all turned out fine.
[Taiki] Yeah, I guess it did.
Whatcha lookin' at, punk? That's ten G's.
You're raising the price?
[Hina laughs] Kidding!
I'm getting more charming by the day!
So make sure that you keep an eye on me.
[vocalizing tune]
Turns out, I was worrying over nothing.
[Kyo] Hm.
As the outside observer in all this,
it feels like it look forever
just to get to this point.
Now it all depends
on Chinatsu's next move.
Good night, sleep well.
- Good night.
- 'Night.
This is really good.
[Taiki] Practice really
tires me out these days.
But with Hina already
earning her spot for nationals,
I need to push harder so I can follow.
[both] Oh.
Heading to bed?
Yeah, how about you?
I'm getting water.
Oh, yeah, got it.
Oh. And by the way,
I saw Hina at the chiropractor today.
What?
Don't tell me that she
ran her mouth at you?
No, she was just thanking me
for the umbrella the other day.
Thank you very much
for your help the other day!
I've started carrying
a foldable umbrella, too, we're twins!
Oh, is that right!
She's amazing, isn't she?
She's a first-year,
and she won prefectural qualifiers.
Although Hina herself
wasn't satisfied with how she did.
Huh?
She said she didn't perform
her routine perfectly.
She was pretty fired up
to iron out all of the kinks,
so she can nail it at nationals.
Hina, a hopeless gymnastics nerd.
[gasps softly]
Ah, okay, right,
I'll be heading to bed, then.
- Sleep well.
- Good night.
[pensive music playing]
He really is a hopeless badminton nerd,
don't ya think, Chinatsu?
The two of them... would be good together.
Hina seems to feel that way about...
That means I'm just getting in the way.
The girl living with the guy.
[gasps softly]
I'm sorry, Hina.
But this is for basketball.
I'm staying his housemate
until I graduate.
[music fades]
[closing theme song playing]